<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_winline">What is Winline?</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description">Winline is a one player puzzle game. It is base on the classic Colour Line game.
        The player can move one ball per turn to a particular place if there is a path (linked set of vertical and
        horizontal empty cells) between the current position of the ball and the desired destination. The goal is to
        score the most points removing balls by forming lines (horizontal, vertical or diagonal) of at least five balls
        of the same colour. If the player does form such lines of at least five balls of the same colour, the balls
        in those lines disappear, adding the number of balls that disappear to the overall player points, and he gains
        one turn, e.g. he can move another ball. If not, three new balls are added (at random colour and position), and
        the game continues until the board is either full or empty.</string>

    <string name="about_winline_description_note">Note: you won\'t get points for a configuration of five or more balls in a row
        if you last moved ball is not part of such configuration (e.g. five or more in a row caused by random allocation
        of the three new balls added).</string>

    <string name="how_to_play">How to play?</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_description">To play you only need to touch on the ball you want to move and then touch in an
        empty cell. If there is a path between the position of the ball and the desired destination the ball will move. You
        also can save your current game touching on the most right button at the board bottom, create a new game using the
        button in the center and load a saved game with the button most to the left.
    </string>

    <string name="how_combo_work">How combo works?</string>
    <string name="how_combo_work_description">The combo feature is a way to give the player the opportunity to increments the points
        by rewarding consecutive scores. Any time the player scores a countdown will be start, during this time a subsequent
        score will multiply the points involved in the score by a number starting in 2 and incrementing consecutively in 1
        and reset the countdown. If the time pass without a score the multiplier will reset to 2.
    </string>
</resources>