<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_winline">What should you know?</string>

    <string name="about_winline_description">Winline is a one player puzzle game.</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description1">The player can move one ball per turn to a particular place if there is path to there</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description2">A path is a linked set of vertical and horizontal empty cells between 2 position.</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description3">The goal is to score points by forming lines (horizontal, vertical or diagonal) of at least five balls
        of the same colour.</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description4">The balls involves in a score will disappear, adding those balls to the player points.</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description5">When you score you gain one turn, e.g. you can move another ball.</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description6">If you move and not score three new balls are added (at random colour and position).</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description7">The game is over either the board is full or empty.</string>
    <string name="about_winline_description8">You won\'t get points for a configuration of five or more balls in a row if you last move isn\'t
        part of such configuration (e.g. five or more in a row caused by random allocation of the three new balls added).</string>

    <string name="guide_step1">Move ball (Step 1)</string>
    <string name="guide_step1_description">To move a ball touch the ball you want to move.</string>


    <string name="guide_step2">Move ball (Step 2)</string>
    <string name="guide_step2_description">After a ball is selected touch on the empty cell you want to move it.</string>

    <string name="guide_step3">Combo score</string>
    <string name="guide_step3_description">The combo give you the opportunity to increments your points during a period of time (10 sec). Any subsequent
        score (during this time) will multiply the points by a multiplier starting in 2 (incrementing consecutively by 1 on each score).
    </string>

    <string name="guide_step4">No score</string>
    <string name="guide_step4_description">If you move a ball without make a score, three new balls will be added to the board at random position.</string>

    <string name="guide_step5">Game record</string>
    <string name="guide_step5_description">Touch the start next to your current score to see your best record.</string>

    <string name="guide_step6">Save game</string>
    <string name="guide_step6_description">You can save your game touching on this button. The game will be on the list of saved games.

    </string><string name="guide_step7">New game</string>
    <string name="guide_step7_description">You can create a new game touching on this button. If your current game isn\'t saved yet a dialog will be warn you
        about it.</string>


    <string name="guide_step8">Select a saved game</string>
    <string name="guide_step8_description">Touch on this button to see the list of your saved games. Here you can see when you saved it, the score and the time
        you spend on it. To select one, just touch on it.</string>



    <string name="winline_help_tour">Try the demo!</string>
</resources>